{
    "Sport": [
        {
            "Question": "Whos the best statistic soccer player?",
            "Answer": "Lionell Messi",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Lionell Messi",
                "Christiano Ronaldo",
                "Zlatan Ibrahimovic"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the name of the thing that ichockey players having on their head?",
            "Answer": "Helmet",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Hat",
                "They dont have anything on their head",
                "Helmet"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "How many players are there on the soccer field in the same time?",
            "Answer": "22",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "11",
                "22",
                "10"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "For how long do a soccergame last?",
            "Answer": "90",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "75",
                "90",
                "45"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Whos the most fameous basketball player",
            "Answer": "Michael Jordan",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Michael Jordan",
                "test1",
                "test1"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Who is the most famous soccer player in Sweden?",
            "Answer": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
                "Alexander Isak",
                "Marcus Berg"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which soccer team won the Swedish league 'Allsvenskan'?",
            "Answer": "MFF",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Djurgården",
                "AIK",
                "MFF"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "In which country do Manchester united play?",
            "Answer": "England",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Sweden",
                "England",
                "Brasil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Do there exist a league with the name 'Challenger League'?",
            "Answer": "No",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which player has the shortname 'CR7'?",
            "Answer": "Christiano Ronaldo",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Christiano Ronaldo",
                "Lionell Messi",
                "Mesut Özil"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "For which country do Robert Lewandowski plays for?",
            "Answer": "Poland",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Germany",
                "French",
                "Poland"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which country do Soccer VM plays in 2022?",
            "Answer": "Qatar",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Brasil",
                "Qatar",
                "Russia"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Programming": [
        {
            "Question": "What is the most common Programming language?",
            "Answer": "C",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "C",
                "Python",
                "Java"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "What is the easiest language to learn?",
            "Answer": "HTML",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "C++",
                "C#",
                "HTML"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "Food": [
        {
            "Question": "What is USA's national dish?",
            "Answer": "Hamburger",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Pizza",
                "Pasta carbonara",
                "Hamburger"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "Based on which grape do you make red wine from?",
            "Answer": "Hamburger",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Blue",
                "Green",
                "Red"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "what year did Mcdonalds started its first restaurant?",
            "Answer": "1940",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "1945",
                "1960",
                "1940"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "What's soda have been sold the most globally?",
            "Answer": "Coca-cola",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Sprite",
                "Coca-cola",
                "DrPepper"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "When did the first ketchup recipie got created?",
            "Answer": "1801",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "1920",
                "1850",
                "1801"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "General": [
        {
            "Question": "Which collage education is thos most popular?",
            "Answer": "Jurist",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "Doctor",
                "Jurist",
                "Kitchener"
            ]
        },
        {
            "Question": "What does the most expensive phone cost?",
            "Answer": "350 000",
            "ExampleAnswers": [
                "350 000",
                "200 000",
                "50 000"
            ]
        }
    ]
}